<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changelog>
  <change version="0.8.5">
    <datetime day-of-week="Thu" month="2" day="21" hour="20"
      minute="12" second="10" timezone="CET" year="2019"/>
    <logentry>Replaced Fira Sans with FiraGO.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fix includes to avoid configure-error when “disable-x11” was active.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixes underscores in markdown documentation.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.8.4">
    <datetime day-of-week="Sun" month="9" day="3" hour="21"
      minute="37" second="2" timezone="CEST" year="2017"/>
    <logentry>Fix superfluous libraries and includes during install when using $DESTDIR, addressing github issue #21.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fix possible buffer overflow when writing score and turn data into status line.</logentry>
    <logentry>Made screen size functions use 16-bit instead of 8-bit values, allowing version 5+ games to work with screen dimensions > 255.</logentry>
    <logentry>Add missing “clean-dev” target.</logentry>
    <logentry>Added missing contributor phrasing to BSD-3 clause. The resulting license now exactly matches the wording used on Github and so also makes the license detection work.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.8.3">
    <datetime day-of-week="Sun" month="4" day="9" hour="10"
      minute="13" second="30" timezone="CEST" year="2017"/>
    <logentry>Adapted to replacement of en_US locale with en_GB from libfizmo.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed missing opening screen and disappearing prompt during timed input in “eliza.z5”. Thanks to Stephen Gutknecht for reporting the problem.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed overlong reverse chars. This corrects several ASCII art problems as in Photopia, Nameless and ZChess, as well as in several opening screens. Thanks to Stephen Gutknecht.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed incomplete flush function in true_type_wordwrapper.c. This corrects the incorrect display of the startup-screens in “AtWork.z5” and “Photopia”. Thanks to Stephen Gutknecht for reporting the problem.</logentry>
    <logentry>Raised version number into 0.8 range to comply with general version scheme for new modules.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.7.3">
    <logentry>Fixed missing display of upper screen output on game start, like, for example, the title display of “Alpha“ or “Anchorhead”.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed missing evaluation of events on start-up. This fixes a bug that made the interpreter crash when your initial screen size was less than the default size. This fix does now also allow resizing the window during frontispiece display.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed build error which occured when "--disable-x11" was set for drilbo.</logentry>
    <logentry>Fixed drawing the scrollbar at invalid positions.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.7.2">
    <datetime day-of-week="Sub" month="10" day="9" hour="12"
      minute="00" second="17" timezone="CEST" year="2016"/>
    <logentry>Improved build system for separate library and interface builds.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.7.1">
    <datetime day-of-week="Wed" month="8" day="31" hour="22"
      minute="39" second="42" timezone="CEST" year="2016"/>
    <logentry>Use tiny-xml-doc-tools for documentation.</logentry>
  </change>

  <change version="0.7.0">
    <datetime day-of-week="Thu" month="7" day="28" hour="19"
      minute="38" second="43" timezone="CEST" year="2016"/>
    <logentry>The “libpixelif” interface translates output from the fizmo Z-Machine to a pixel-based interface by using the freetype2 engine, providing proportional font display, antialiasing, and subpixel-rendering along with HiDPI support.</logentry>
    <logentry>It uses the “Fira Sans” and “Fira Mono” font faces which were made by Erik Spiekermann and Ralph du Carrois.</logentry>
  </change>
</changelog>

